[
    {
        "question": "Help",
        "response": "Sorry, I'm currently under works.",
        "timestamp": 1669118409
    },
    {
        "question": "why",
        "response": "Sorry, I'm currently under works.",
        "timestamp": 1669118440
    },
    {
        "question": "j",
        "response": null,
        "timestamp": 1669463288
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "response": null,
        "timestamp": 1669463330
    },
    {
        "question": "sd",
        "response": null,
        "timestamp": 1669463342
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "response": null,
        "timestamp": 1669463351
    },
    {
        "question": "hello",
        "response": "10:50 PM",
        "timestamp": 1669463414
    },
    {
        "question": "hello",
        "response": "Sorry. I don't know what you're asking for",
        "timestamp": 1669463472
    },
    {
        "question": "time",
        "response": "10:51 PM",
        "timestamp": 1669463477
    },
    {
        "question": "hlelo",
        "response": "Sorry. I don't know what you're asking for",
        "timestamp": 1669463566
    },
    {
        "question": "time",
        "response": "10:52 PM",
        "timestamp": 1669463566
    },
    {
        "question": "hello",
        "response": "Sorry. I don't know what you're asking for",
        "timestamp": 1669463585
    },
    {
        "question": "What's the time?",
        "response": "10:53 PM",
        "timestamp": 1669463585
    },
    {
        "question": "hello",
        "response": "Sorry. I don't know what you're asking for",
        "timestamp": 1669463989
    },
    {
        "question": "what;s the time",
        "response": "The time is 10:59 PM\nWhat a great time to go to sleep",
        "timestamp": 1669463989
    },
    {
        "question": "What;s the time",
        "response": "The time is 11:00 PM.\nWhat a great time to go to sleep!",
        "timestamp": 1669464006
    },
    {
        "question": "sHut yo bitch ass up",
        "response": "Sorry. I don't know what you're asking for",
        "timestamp": 1669464006
    }
]